Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/mluan-nguyen (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Solution Architecture
Business Management
Leadership

Languages

English (Full Professional)
Vietnamese (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Bachelor of Information Technology
HashiCorp Certified: Terraform
Associate (003)
Professional Diploma of IT
HP Accredited Systems Engineer
NetApp Data ONTAP 7-mode
administration

Honors-Awards

Special Recognition Award for Graduates with Outstanding Academic

Annual Scholarships
Quarter Scholarships
Total Scholarship by NIIT Institute
Top Scorers University entrance
exam

Luan Nguyen

Senior Infrastructure | Cloud | DevOps Engineer | MBA Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

A person who puts his passion in technology. He always pursuits of helping people to provide best solutions and apply technology to improve business efficiency and human life.

14-year working in IT Services, wide experiences in IT infrastructures, services and scripting, ... are strengths that allow me to be able to deep dive into any technologies and confidently undertake any projects that organization needs. I am looking for a chance to contribute my passions and efforts to our success.

Fast learners, dare to do, ethical, critical thinking, Independent and teamwork are some characteristics you might find at me. :)

Experience

Bosch Global Software Technologies Vietnam Squad Lead / Senior Cloud and DevOps Engineer January 2022 - Present (3 years 3 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Lead Cloud & DevOps team for excellence, customer satisfaction, and growth.

- Lead the team to deliver customer-aligned outcomes; mentor/ develop team members; and handle escalations;
- Work on multi-projects to consult, deploy, maintain infra on Clouds;
- Lead, consult, and implement DevOps, IaC and automation projects.

Saigon South International School Technical Solutions Engineer / CAS Leader March 2018 - January 2022 (3 years 11 months) Vietnam

- Responsible for whole IT infrastructure including 50 Windows, Linux servers, networks, apps, clouds and IT services for over 1500 users;
- Technical architect and solution designer;
- Product owner of the core internal automated apps;
- DevOps and systems integration engineer of internal projects.

Page 1 of 3

Teamwork Management Vietnam Infrastructure Team leader September 2016 - March 2018 (1 year 7 months) Vietnam

- Responsible for whole IT infrastructure including +1000 servers, SAN worldwide working well and efficiently;
- Made sure L2/L3 service requests are solved timely;
- Daily monitor, evaluated and improved workflow and infrastructure;
- Monitored, managed the infra and worked with incidents / changes.

Advance Vision Technology
Network & Systems Engineer
December 2014 - September 2016 (1 year 10 months)
Vietnam, Australia, China, Malaysia

- Presale, consulted IT solutions for VN customers;
- Onsite and delivered projects in VN, CN, AU and ASEAN;
- Handled L2/ L3 service requests for VN, CN and AU customers;
- Designed and managed company internal infrastructure in VN.

NTT Communications Systems Integration Engineer October 2013 - December 2014 (1 year 3 months) Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

- Presale, consulted IT solutions for VN market;
- · Audited, designed and implemented projects for VN and Japan customers;
- Managed entire projects, responsible for their success.

Prism Information Technology Services
Technical Engineer / BKaaS Lead
October 2011 - September 2013 (2 years)

- · Product leader of Backup as a Service;
- Designed backup platform for BKaaS cloud infrastructure;
- Presale, consulted IT and cloud solutions for VN market;
- Designed, configured and monitored cloud infrastructure;
- Handled IT service requests, delivered IT project to customers.

Hoa Sen University
Teaching Assistant
October 2011 - January 2012 (4 months)
Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

- Coordinated with professors to build up course and improve teaching quality;
- Took care of C programming classes, led and taught student in class;
- Checked and marked student exams.

Education

University Of Economics Ho Chi Minh City
Master of Business Administration - MBA · (2021 - 2022)

Hoa Sen University

Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.), Computer Software Engineering · (2008 - 2012)

National Institute of Information Technology
Associate of Science (A.S.), Network and System Administration/
Administrator · (2009 - 2012)